

♣ Profile

Well-qualified mobile developer with advanced skills on Flutter and Android. Studying Clean Architecture, SOLID, TDD, Design Patterns and Refactoring. I'm committed to the best way to produce high-quality softwares, following good principles and techniques of the Software Engineering. I have more than 3 years of related experience with software development.

★ Favorite technologies



Employment history

Mobile developer at Bean Softwares

March 2021 - Present

Fullstack developer at Thalamus Digital

July 2020 - June 2021

Mobile developer at MFIT Personal

January 2020 - May 2020

Education

Computer Science at Univali

February 2020 - Present

Courses

English at KNN Idiomas

September 2020 - Present

Projects

Entrepreneur at iCut

May 2021 - Present

A barber appointment app. Available on icut.app.

Voluntary coding instructor

May 2021 - Present

Entrepreneur at StudentPlus

August 2018 - April 2021

A study planner. Available on Google Play.

Details

Itajaí, SC, Brazil contact@lucasbatista.me

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

WhatsApp

Website

Skills

UI/UX Design

TDD

DevOps

UML

Design Patterns

SOLID

Clean Architecture

Languages

English

Hobbies

Hackathons, pair programming, teaching, code kata and reading.